{
    "subject": "resource/Speedy_West",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Speedy West is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9877870678901672,
            "question": "Is United States considered the hometown of Speedy West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9409151077270508,
            "question": "What is the hometown of Speedy West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020351767539978,
            "question": "Is Speedy West from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8818586468696594,
            "question": "Is Speedy West an American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6414145231246948,
            "question": "Where was Speedy West born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6209996938705444,
            "question": "Where did Speedy West grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5603233575820923,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Speedy West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5361666083335876,
            "question": "To which country does Speedy West belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4653276205062866,
            "question": "What is the origin of Speedy West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37706321477890015,
            "question": "In which country does Speedy West call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Speedy West is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_497_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin of Speedy West?",
            "html": "dbpedia_497_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Speedy West belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_497_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Speedy West?",
            "html": "dbpedia_497_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_497_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Speedy West, including his birth and death locations (Springfield, Missouri, and Broken Arrow, Oklahoma, both in the United States), which supports the claim that the hometown of Speedy West is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Speedy West's hometown is explicitly stated as Springfield, Missouri, USA, within the context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states Speedy West's hometown is the United States, but context information specifies his birthplace as Springfield, Missouri, USA.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It directly contradicts statement 1 where it clearly mentions \"Speedy West was born on 25 January 1924 in Springfield, Missouri, USA.\" indicating his hometown as the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Speedy West was born in Springfield, Missouri, USA, indicating his hometown is in the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}